<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest on Bon Aqua Computer Club</title>
    <link>https://bonaqua.club/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest on Bon Aqua Computer Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 11:00:19 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bonaqua.club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bonaqua.club/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bonaqua.club/about/</guid>
      <description>The Bon Aqua Computer Club is an opportunity to meet and collaborate on fun technical projects that expand our minds and enhance our self-reliance. We can each have a hand in taking back our sovereignty if we join together and commit to learning about what opportunities are out there!
 Background  Bon Aqua Computer Club is owned &amp;amp; operated by Andrew Grathwohl.  I moved to Bon Aqua from New York, NY, where I spent most of my childhood and adult years until the COVID-19 lockdowns began taking place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Your Mouth: Summer Porch Tour 2021</title>
      <link>https://bonaqua.club/posts/rym-spt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 11:00:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bonaqua.club/posts/rym-spt/</guid>
      <description>The first live event at the Bon Aqua Computer Club was a resounding success, and put us on an amazing trajectory for future endeavors.
 We kicked the night off with some standup sets by BK Chris, followed by Robbie TheFire Bernstein.
Much light was made of the fact that I was run over by a car in Nashville the previous day.
Next, we did a live Run Your Mouth podcast, where I presented a one-time-only slide deck about Bill Gates and why he is evil in far more ways than one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
